

A SANDHYA RANI SUBUDHI

DEVELOPER



Berhampur, Odisha



sandhyasubudhi26@gmai.



+91-7008815236



/in/a-sandhya-ranisubudhi-a6890b16a

PROFILE

I am a qualified and professional developer with 2+ years of experience in IT industry, worked in developing and maintaining the web application. Looking forward to engance my skills and apply knowledge in achieving organization's goal.

SKILLS

HTML CSS

React JS

Node JS

PostgreSQL

Git

Grafana

WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR DEVELOPER

Wipro

Sep 2022 - Present

Client - BT

- Leading the team with 2+ developers.
- Working on handling client code.
- Focus on adding new features, quickly fixing bugs and fulfilling client requirements on time.

DEVELOPER

WIPRO

Sep 2020 - Sep 2022

Client - BT

Tools and Technologies-

Reactjs, Nodejs, PostgreSQL, Grafana, PgAdmin, Git, Postman, VS Code

- Working as Full-Stack developer handling both frontend and back-end of the application.
- Working on handling client code and adding functionality to the application as per client requirement.
- Created secured API using JWT to implement CRUD operation.
- Implemented Redis cache to improve application performance.
- Created Grafana Dashboard to display data in readable format.
- Received awards and recognition for my work from Client and Senior Leads.

EDUCATION HISTORY

Bachelor in Technology

2016-2020

National Institute of Science & Technology